<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ciaran1111</title>
    <link>https://ciaran1111.git.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ciaran1111</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 19:36:35 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ciaran1111.git.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CMP102(Software Design)</title>
      <link>https://ciaran1111.git.io/post/cmp102/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 19:36:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciaran1111.git.io/post/cmp102/</guid>
      <description>CMP102, was on evolution on the previous C++ module. This module most notably took a look into concepts such as object orintated programming. The end assingment for CMP102 was to create a darts simmulation program. Which would simulate a set amount of games between two fictional players and determin how many games each player would have won based up hit rate of said player. My submission was awared an A+. A snippet is bellow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMP104( Programming with C&#43;&#43;)</title>
      <link>https://ciaran1111.git.io/post/cmp104/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 19:21:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciaran1111.git.io/post/cmp104/</guid>
      <description>This was one of the first modules apart of my course and was also my first real experience with C++. The module is designed for all levels of programmers to help people familiarise themselves with C++ before moving onto more complex programs in later years. Having programmed before with python, java and visual basic(in school) i found myself being ahead of the module. The main assignment was to create a cyber pet game which the aim was to keep your pet alive by allowing to sleep and eat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMP110</title>
      <link>https://ciaran1111.git.io/post/cmp110/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 19:19:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciaran1111.git.io/post/cmp110/</guid>
      <description>Intro to security research paper lorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsumlorum ipsum</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
